Don Alfons Nisnoni Resume

PERSONAL DATA



Date of Birth: 18 September 1995 (26 years old) **Address:** Semangka street, Amnesi, Kota Raja subdistrict, Kupang city, East Nusa Tenggara province,

Indonesia

Phone: +6282147747572

Preffered Position: Front-end web developer, Backend web developer or Full-stack web developer

Email: donalfonsnnisnoni@gmail.com **Website:** donnisnoni.github.io

GitHub: donnisnoni

LinkedIn: don-alfons-nisnoni-b753b2201

SUMMARY

Hello!

Hi there! My name is Don Alfons Nisnoni. I'm a software developer from Indonesia.

I mostly do full-stack web development on my daily programming activity. I learn web development since 2015 when web programming lecture is introduced to me on my campus. By the way I prefer to be called as a software developer rather than web developer because I'm also experienced and open to do another kinds of programming. But to be honest, I'm more experienced as a web developer.

Fresh graduate

I just graduated back in november 2020 with GPA of 3.47. Actually, I finished my college on december 2019. But because of COVID-19 pandemic, the graduation ceremony is postponed.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

Jul 2015 - Dec 2019 - **GPA: 3.47** - Graduated on Nov 2020 due COVID-19

SKILLS

Thing's that I've touch so far:

Software/Tools:

Git, GitHub, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, PostCSS, Hugo SSG

Databases:

Redis, MySQL & MariaDB

Programming Languages:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Typescript, C#, V, SASS, SQL, PHP

Frameworks/Libraries:

jQuery, Vue, Svelte, Sapper, Codelgniter, Laravel, Express, Fastify, Sequelize, TailwindCSS

Technique:

Responsive Web Desing, a11y, i18n, PWA

EXPERIENCES

Software Engineer

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 @ **STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang**

- Build a website for improve student's online services
- Upgrade & improve campus main website
- Create work email for lecturer's
- Analyze and improve existing campus websites security and UI
- Upgrade campus tech stacks

Part-time Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2020 - Present @ Vlingo

• Implementing vlingo/auth UI